So hello, welcome to Traders Diary. It is the
midweek session and the overall
mood today is quite cheap.
India is lacking news. The numbers were
not that high today, they were not that high yesterday either, so some
stops have been taken.
And this time, there was a
constant competition going on as to
who would be the first to be late if any news came. So, whatever
news you have seen,
we will play a very traditional game on it.
Along with this, if you tell me
how is the global outlook looking to you? Globally, if
you talk about yesterday or what is being
seen today, what kind of atmosphere is being seen
there too, it is very cheap, whether
you talk about the American markets, and
we are seeing its exact indications on Nifty as well.
Almost flat sir
high is showing 50 with a fall of 1920 ranks.
Trading is
seen happening here right now and if you look at the two zones, in
this way, a little
buying is seen returning here, but
Largely, the sentiment seems to be forming a flat
band. If you look at the other side, there was a
fall like this at the top and
that fall was only a little bit
during the whole day. So, there does
not seem to be much support for the tax shares there in the current session.
And
if you look at the European market as well, the trend from there is
not very positive either.
However, if you look at yesterday's session, all the three
indices were seen trading in the green mark. So, there are
some good signs from the European market. But
lastly, now we have to see that the
figure of the fee was seen in yesterday's 17. There was selling of about
810-812 crores here in the cash market.
And the story is not the story,
expectations are that
here in China, the GDP figure that came out yesterday was estimated at 4%,
they gave a Q1 GDP of 4.5%, so it is possible that the
fee can be seen increasing its positions here in the middle of China
in the times to come because at present this is what we are
seeing.  For the last two-three months, you have seen the
story of China reopening becoming a big positive
for global institutional investors. But you will have to
see what is the mood in the future because the
story of India is also quite interesting and if
Fiji is making a mistake then you will have to see
how big a game can be played here in the future.
But right now the scenario is
that the mood is almost cheap in the global market. There is
not much fluctuation. The readings are heavy
sessions will also be seen starting in the red from next week.
But this week
also keep in mind that Reliance numbers are
also going to come, so you will have to see its
impact. How will the Reliance numbers affect the
entire market today and what will be the mood like.
But the way the scenario is right now,
tell us how many buys and how many bets did you place and which is your first stock you have
chosen. Also tell the viewers that
if you see the biggest news of today,
Involt Tax, on the basis of this, if you will see
two are written, meaning one put option has been taken, rest
overall you will see that all the rest are buys now.
First, if we talk about the category, it is what kind of
stock. In what kind of stock, the stock I have
taken is properties. Now,
if you look at it today, the listing of BML Land Assets is going to happen.
If the listing is going to happen, then
overall, if you look at
properties, they also have a
plant bank in it and if you look at their
Q1 major result, when the result came, on
page number six, they have
mentioned the value of their land there, it is
around ₹10,000 ₹600 crores. But
if you do the share value, then
according to that, it comes around ₹300. And if the
current prices are visible, then it was
not around ₹10000, it is
visible around ₹90, 93, so the
discount is approximately 70%. So, if
you see the listing of BML Land Assets getting
a little good, going above ₹250, then it is
possible that
momentum comes here too. See, you saw a
good momentum coming yesterday also, hence we are taking advantage of
properties from this.  They will buy, will
keep the target of 96 and will keep the top loss at
92. Absolutely, the
listing of Land Acid is about to happen, keeping that in
mind, it is
advisable to buy properties here.
Let me tell you how
Som is commenting on this counter. Actually, yesterday the company has
given the news that a capacity expansion has been done at one of their subsidiaries
in Karnataka and the commercial operations,
commercial production, have started there, so
commercial production will be
seen coming. The company has said that
they will be getting full benefit from it.
Anyway, if you
look at the counter, it is continuously in bullish momentum
and is tweeting almost around 160. So,
very good buying from the emerging stars is
seen distributed here and the
story is not a story, the little bullishness that was seen in yesterday's session is
continuing today as well.
Like, you can see the impact of the news on this counter today as
well, so there are
good opportunities to buy here.
Set a target of 165, you have to keep a stop of 156.
Let's move ahead and  Here, let us
talk about the stops we have chosen in the derivatives space. First of all,
from my side, in the features category, there is the
JSW Steel counter. Now,
on the metal space, I have been continuously characterizing for the last two-three weeks. On
April 11, I had told you about the
Hindalco counter and since then, you should
see what kind of a divided rally has been seen there
and now I feel that
you may see a rally in the steel counter as well in the future
because the
way things are happening in the clear American market, the
metals are seen doing a little out of range there as well.
In yesterday's session also, there was a good
rally of about 1 1/2 to 2%, so
JSW Steel,
keeping this in mind, can be a good buying opportunity for you. So,
keep a target of 740 here as well. 712 is your stock
plus see, if we talk specifically about metals, if we
talk about steel only, then if the
story of China is good, then almost
50% of the production is of them in all the metals, so
if there is a little  It is a very good stock,
so for other companies if
even 10% increase occurs then it becomes a big deal, so
definitely your star which
you have been giving continuously is very good, the
futures which I have sold is
Reliance, now what is the reason for this because if
you see the news that
64% has been imposed as simple tax on domestic production,
so if you see logically here, if
you see then this is a negative news
for them, on this star I will
also give another stock, according to that you have to
sell the futures of Reliance, the
target will be 200 seven and if we
keep this topless then this is 375 and in similar pay
options, if I buy the put option, that
is ONGC, similar star here
also if you see the voltage which
looks good, you see it increasing a lot,
after that
you see 64% coming there, here also
if you see this for them also, it is a negative story, there is a
negative tax, hence
ONGC  We will also buy the put option of 160
which is getting you around 1.4,
we will keep the target of 1.85 and will keep the stop loss at 1.25. So let's
go ahead,
Armaan is keeping an eye on these two outer stocks, Reliance and ONGC. The
way the win-loss tax on crude oil is
seen increasing again, so the story
here is that
you may see selling here, so let's move ahead with this
and I have selected the stock.
In the options category, the numbers of ICC Lombard are
looking quite good,
especially if you talk from the profit point of view, there has been a
growth of 40% here,
whereas the street estimate and our estimate was
also around 340 crores, the
company has registered a profit of 437 crores. There has been
a good premium growth in the health segment
and I was checking their results, then
their line
item of commissioner, especially in total expenses,
shows it increasing directly from 160 crores to 90 crores, the
line item of commissioner plus brokerage is
clear,  The indications are that
their expenses have reduced here, the benefit of this is
seen coming to the bottom line, so for
this reason, buy on such foxes here, keep doing it, the
net premium has
increased further from around 12:30, there
is a tomorrow option of 1140, buy buy available at 28
for a target of 45 and your stop will be ₹20
here, so let's start
with the options stock, so from my side, first
tomorrow is ABFRL i.e. Aditya Birla
Fashion and Retail, here I feel
that the tax sector is showing continuous weakness
and if you look at the long chart right now, 3 months, 6
months, you can see continuous downtrend
here,
friends, I am seeing a weak
counter and if there is selling again from the market today, then it is
possible that the unbinding that has been happening here in the
absence, may be seen continuing today as well,
in yesterday's session also there was a
band of selling in the red mark.  The opinion
is for a target of only Rs 218 on the tax structure
and the stop that you have to make on the higher side will be of
Rs 228. So,
look at this techno pick from my side.
If you talk about the techno pick, then the comparison
chart which is compatible is looking good
because if you wanted to overall, then its
chart is looking interesting. You will
see that for some time if you see, the
momentum that has come is written well for you.
Even yesterday if we look at it,
you saw a rise of around 2% only. So overall
if you look at it from the space, then this target
you have to keep is 125 and stop loss should be kept at
120.95 because if you look at the technicals,
you are looking sound. Now the matter has come to fund
out the fundamental stock. It has been
taken according to the fund in the fundamentals, that is ICC
Prudential. Look, overall if you talk about this stock
or why not talk about this space,
this space story is for time, not just for one
year or two years, it is for many times.  The
reason is that if you look at some
points which are not
just specific to this company but are
very important for this sector, if you
look at the percentage of GDP of Sum Assured, then if you
look at the insurance space, I am
talking about life insurance, then
our country accounts for approximately 22%, if you look at it, it comes to
approximately 250%,
this will be on one side, on the other hand, if you
look at the protection gap, how much protection
we need and what is the difference in it, then
if
you look at it for our country, it comes to approximately 83%,
whereas in Indonesia, their
number there is also 76%, which means it is even lower than that,
you will have a lot in this space,
if you look at the text, new
tax definitely, if you see that
this happened due to the impact of the news, it appears that there is a
slight loss of interest in the sector,
then this thing, you are buying a life insurance
policy, you are
buying it for the long term,
not just to save tax.  Obviously, if
you look at it specifically on a long term basis, then
you will see good momentum coming in this company in the compatibility space.
For the long term, I am
giving a duration of only one year, but you should keep this
strong stock in your portfolio continuously
and in every downturn, you should
buy a little bit here. The target will be
550% and the duration will be one year.
Fundamentally, I like the proof from this,
Kushal, what do you like? Look here,
Armaan, the funda pick from my side, so I was
repeatedly seeing that
Mahindra and Mahindra, you should
focus on it a lot now and move back.
I feel that the decline that was there is over now, the
outside risk story has now
bottomed out and the
growth triggers for the future are looking quite impressive. The
company has also said
that by 2027,
about 20 to 30% of its portfolio, that is,
20 to 30% of the entire passenger vehicle will be
electric.  It will be seen happening, they
also launched their XUV 400 and they have already seen getting a
great response there
and anyway we
know the history that Mahindra &
Mahindra came here as a pioneer
when they launched their SUV, the
initial Ila, in 2010.
Their A car was seen coming
but obviously that time was not mature enough for
adoption to happen that fast
but like Tata Motors, they have taken the lead now.
It is possible that Mahindra itself may come
out with the second best car to further increase
its market shares.
Currently their
portfolio is not that big but if these
people capitalize on this thing and the
management also comes out with a big Fox like
statement, it seems that 2017 is
not too far, I think there is a gap of 4 years
and the scenario that is prevailing right now is that all the
auto component players are
also continuously increasing their Avi and the
portfolio size of the Avi kit.  I have
heard that you like BMW a lot,
I know that if you have to keep two stocks which are the
best in this space, then
who else would you keep other than BMW,
friend, now first comes Motors, but
Lali, I like Eminem more
because the way his execution has been,
especially in the SUV portfolio, going forward,
TV is obviously a matter of transmission and
if Mahindra & Mahindra is applying it too, then
on the designing front,
they have not faced any competition historically,
in the SUV portfolio, which is the
biggest preferred demand of the consumers in today's session,
so
you are continuously seeing a huge waiting period on it, that is
going on here and Mahindra & Mahindra, I
think, whatever their SUV portfolio is right now, there is already a
waiting period of six to eight months, the
scenario is that Mahindra & Mahindra,
you should focus on it, along with this
Tarak that has come from Eminem,
you should also take a big focus on Tata Motors,
so
Eminem can be a good opportunity for me to buy N fundep in the next
one year and I feel that in the next one year,
you should target 1400 and then move ahead by choosing the fundamentals.
Let's move ahead and our next
category is IPL.
In the IPL space, from my side, the
stock is Britannia.
It was on my radar for quite some time but now I have gathered some
courage because
if you look at the portfolio of Britannia, it is the
portfolio of biscuits. The kind of fall in Pan Oil that
we have seen in the last few days is also good, that is a big support
and the consumption story is there. Basically, if
you look at the FMCG space, it should be seen moving forward with strength.
You should definitely see it tomorrow.
Despite having such a big counter of almost 3:30 the day before yesterday, the games of 3:30 the day before yesterday were
seen, so
you can find that a little praiseworthy. The scenario is being created for them here
and Britannia seems to me that for the
long term, definitely
Nivedita.  You can do it, there
is no fundamental problem and for the future, I am feeling
that in the next 12 months, at
least 10 to 15% of the games will be achieved by buying
Britannia for the target of Rs 4900. If we
talk about Britain, when the minute status release
started playing, if you look at those few stocks, at that
time Britannia was my bone of content
stock, the targets were also achieved there,
then after that, now Kushal is handling it further and metal
definitely and generally if you look at the
consumption space, if you talk specifically, then if you talk about the
elections, if you talk about
its period, then if you
see the consumption in general, then it is good, so
according to that, it is definitely a good but a
good company, as per the IPL stock, the
stock which I like is Prestige
State Project, now here I will
tell you some things which you should know
in the presentation and installation, firstly,
how many upcoming projects do they have, approximately 43
What is the area of ​​upcoming projects? 93
billion square feet. If you talk about
how many projects they are completing till now?
What was its area yesterday? 278,
2016 five minutes square feet, which means
more than half of it. Right now, there are upcoming
projects of 9 months. If you
look at the press releases,
you saw the highest sales, you saw the
highest collection, you saw everything going
well. If you look at the 81% of
inventory that they have launched in the last 12 months,
you will see a good amount of inventory there.
Look at the TV, the trust of the institutions
here is around 30-31%. So,
if you look at such companies whose brand
value is very good, where you can see the
outlook coming from the consumers
because in the new projects,
you will see good momentum in that space as well. It has been
coming from the consumers
and in such branches, if you
see that there is a continuous demand for new projects,
there is a lot  It is also going well
and if you
look at the compatibility, if we get a good comparative
valuation there, then the
Prestige Status project becomes a
good thing, in this we will keep the duration
of 12 mins and the target will be 5:30, of
course and in the mother and
estate space, it is
considered a premium story, keeping in mind the kind of
projects that come, there is
positivity about Prestige Status here and also the way the
rates have paused and the demand is increasing consistently, what is your feeling about
real estate, because you track real estate, so
what is your inclination on this,
I would like to know whether I can also buy any
stock, no no, look, I would tell
you maybe not, if you think that it was a year or two
ago, it was a year ago,
when it is not even a year ago, if you
look at the Bengal report of all these companies which was
released, then one thing was also told by you through your link,
you have read the
annual report of Effort 22 of all these companies,
which are body rest companies.  One
thing everyone said is that we feel that this
big cycle, the stagnation in real estate,
this cycle seems to be coming back
and this is not just about one company, you can
look at the offer guarantee of any company,
pick up any company and see, all the big companies were saying the same thing in
common and now the rate has become posited
like a red pose, so that real estate was
one of the sectors where you will see that the day was
very good
continuously and you were seeing
this even before that, however if you talk about some premium
projects, then the
burning of the tax advantage also happened
on March 31, but as much as I have
talked to a few brokers, they are
giving from the oil perspective that the
demand for real estate lovers and real estate is very good and there is a good
demand, so according to that, there is a
lot of police in the compatibility in real estate,
now we go by the news, according to the news, the
stock that I have taken is
Enterprises because as if you
see that 4k continuously you are getting share holding updates.
They are coming and going. Here the
share of the fishery is congratulations. How much congratulations, it has
increased from 2.5% to around 3%. Let's
not just talk about this cotton. If you
look at this photo, the share
is there, if you look at the total number of shares, then
you will see that it has also increased from 50 to around 60.
Even before that, if you look at it, it
was 2.21 in June, then later in September it was 2.2.
Now if you look at it, you will see it is around 3%. So
here
we are continuously thinking about the fishery that
we are facing problem due to this thing that they are divesting. So, in
some such stocks,
if they are increasing their share gradually, then
there you get a
little compatibility convention. So according to this news, we have to
buy Welfare Enterprises. We will keep the
target at 140 and the stop loss at
124.2. Well, of course, Bill
Span Enterprises is seen being bought by the fishery.
Keeping this thing in mind, you can buy here today.
Stock Life is from my side on the news.  Science, now you
see, there is news that
they have received final approval for that drug.
Now, if you look at the annual sales of
this drug, it is not very big in America, it is worth
around 15 crores.
But the way the pharma space
is in full momentum, you see yesterday also this counter
seems to have moved almost up to 3%. Lupin
Normal showed a rise of 6-30%
and D cross the board form buying is
also seen coming back, so sector
reversal is a big support for it, so
even if there is any small news on the positive side, then
it may be
seen translating into big games for the counter, so
just life sense, for this reason,
buy here for the target of 530. You have to keep a stop here at 5008. Let's move
towards our last and final category, My Choice. And I will tell you about the stocks that I have selected in the My Choice category.
Let me first give you a weak point yesterday and
that is LT Maitri. If you look at it,
I am continuously bullish on the IT counters
and the way the mood is right now,
after the numbers of TCS and Infosys, I
feel that LT is still a
candidate for selling. Although in yesterday's session,
if you look at it, you saw a
good rally and a good rebound in two-three counters,
but the LTA sentiment is
not visible at all supporting it,
so going forward, its
numbers may
appear to be worse than what is expected, so it is possible that
investors are still continuing with the big one here. There is
continuous weakness on the chart, so keep trading here
for the target of 4200
and your stock will become plus. The
second point is 4370 on SBI. Here
you are advised to buy. Actually, if you
look at the banks, in the market decline,
especially if you look at the PSU banks, there is a
big support here, that is seen in the
updates that came from Bank of Baroda.  Even then I had
told you about this counter and yesterday at 17
it was also in a bullish mood, so
overall the scenario remains the same
for the entire banking space, my opinion is still intact to buy
SBI, the market's leading PSU bank,
set a target of ₹560 for today
and ₹535 will be your stop loss and the last one is tomorrow, I am
forming an opinion to buy IGL
because here a positive broker
report has come and that is
from Morgan Stanley and the pricing on IGL is
around 495, you
should buy it and
put a stock plus for the target of 520, see
Mike, I have taken two stops in this first, that is the
blue star, both of its asterisks,
you will continuously see that news has come, there is a
hit, its story is the same
in the states or in the areas,
you have a hit disease,
if you look at it according to the heat, it is continuously
increasing and overall if you look at it  If we
look at it from this aspect, then for both these
companies, the color is for both of them,
so it is possible that
you will see good business
coming in here comparatively. For Voltas, we will buy the
target and keep a duration of 950 and 6
mina. Similarly, Blue Star is also to be
bought here. We will keep a target of 1650 and a
duration of 6 mina. And the third and
last stock that we have bought is GIC
because Tarak is the same, from this, it has been
flying from the Jummar side. Some have given that
their results are seen to be quite big. So,
if you see, GIC
may be compatible and if the results are
seen to be better, then you will have to buy GIC here. We will
keep a target of 150 and a stop
of 145. So, the story, the story
scenario, here also seems to be of good strength for GIC. As we have
seen the results coming in from this, so let us tell you that we have
told you about all the stocks of this category, but a
quick recap of all our categories.  Let's do that
first of all, let me
show you the positive update of the company like Som Distilleries, that is
quite good on capacity expansion, there is an update here
that commercial production has started, along with this
in the metal counters, JSW Steel,
all the metal counts are already looking positive, I am
advised to buy the tomorrow option of ICC Lombard 1140 here also, the way the
numbers have come now, there is a
continuous week chart structure, so let's go
here, Mahindra and Mahindra is
looking good for the long, Britannia is being liked in IPL stock,
FM 3G is a good
play, go and buy the life science paper, see the
positive news coming here
and in the Mike Just category, there are bikes in lt93,
but you are advised to buy SBI and fellow IGL
and the
best pick among all these is Mahindra and Mahindra, it can
show a target of 1400 in the next 1 year,
I feel that we
can see the market share going forward, the way the
bookings of XUV 400 are, let's do a
recap, we will see it in cash, properties are
good  Reliance's features in futures are going to
help because when the
news of Infinity came, it was also seen.
If you look at the options, then
you will have to buy the put option of ONGC.
Technically, Mallapuram Finance is
looking good. Fundamentally, the ICC
proof space is also good. In
terms of IPL stocks, Prestige Strait
Project is also looking very good.
According to the news, Bachpan Enterprises,
where the price is high, is big.
If you look at both Voltas and Blue Star,
you
can see the momentum coming from Hitesh's news. And finally,
if you talk about GIC, where the
result of Lombard is there, you will
see the benefit. My
best pick among all these would be Prestige Strait
Project, which is very good
and the brand of the company is also very good. So, look at
Prestige Strait Projects accordingly.
Now, if you look at the company, it has grown.
Still, as you said, even now, if
you look at the global market or
in our market, there are many such projects.  If
you need clarity, then let's go for all that clarity.
We have already joined Deepsar and are
in a bit of a mood.
After a big rally, the global markets have also become a bit bearish.
Our markets are also
showing consolidation trade from both sides, as if there has been a
hat-trick of consolidation today or
you can try to break out of the range in the middle exception.
What are the signals
and where do they keep an eye on, let's tell you this. Let's
start Sher Bazaar Live
[Music]